They're Back... For Everyone Who Believes In the Beat.
Breakin' 2: Electric Boogaloo is a drama, music
film directed by Sam Firstenberg.
The dance crew from "Breakin'" bands together to save a community center from a
greedy developer bent on building a shopping center in its place.
Kelly, played by Lucinda Dickey.
Ozone, played by Adolfo Quinones.
Turbo, played by Michael Chambers.
Rhonda, played by Susie Coelho.
Byron, played by Harry Caesar.
Mrs. Bennett, played by Jo De Winter.
Breakin' 2: Electric Boogaloo is a 1984 American breakdancing musical film directed by Sam Firstenberg that is a
sequel to Breakin', released seven months earlier the same year by the same producers, The Cannon Group.
In markets where the earlier film was titled Breakdance, the sequel
was released as Breakdance 2: Electric Boogaloo.
Another sequel, Rappin' (also known as Breakdance 3), was produced but with an unconnected
plot and different lead characters; only Ice-T appears in all three films.
The subtitle "Electric Boogaloo" has entered the popular-culture lexicon
as a snowclone nickname to denote an archetypal sequel.
The tone is emotional.